>> Brian Holt: 打开控制台仅为秒。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Open your console for
just a second.
我要停止我的服务器但是你也可以打开一个新的终端
I'm gonna stop my server, but you could
just open a new terminal as well.
我说 npm 安装 -D
I'm gonna say npm install -D
eslint-plugin-hook-hook。
eslint-plugin-react-hooks.
>> Brian Holt: 这是 React 团队关于写挂钩的正式规则。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is official rules
from the React team about writing hooks.
>> Brian Holt: 我想给你介绍几个这些。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I want to
introduce you to a couple of these.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，请立即打开您的 ESLint 配置，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
open your ESLint config really quick, and
在规则里面我们要加添几个
here inside of the rules,
we're going to add a couple of them,
和挂钩 / 规则挂钩，我们希望有 2 个错误。
react-hooks/rules-of-hooks, and
we want that 2 error.
因此， 2 将使其出错， >> Brian Holt: And
So 2 will make it error on that,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
我们也要把它加到插件上。
we also I need to add
it to plugins as well.
>> Brian Holt: 反应挂钩，如那样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: react-hooks, like that.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，我在笔记中遗漏了其中一个，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
I am missing one of them here in my notes,
我们去找吧
let's just go find it.
ESLint React， plug-in React 挂钩，这是一个。
ESLint React,
plug-in React hooks, this one.
> > Brian Holt: 我在这里还有一个应该在里面的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And I have another one
here that we should have in there.
这些都是最详尽的
These ones, exhaustive depths.
>> Brian Holt: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So put in that one as well.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会做 1个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we'll do 1.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
this one is going to force you to,
我们稍后会做的，但它与事实有关。
we'll actually about later, but
it has to do with the facts.
所以，再一次提醒你， 0 就关了， 1 号穿了，
So again, just to remind you,
0 is turn off, 1 is worn, and
2 是错的对吧
2 is make it an error, right?
所以任何时候只要你把钩子弄乱
So anytime that you mess up
rule of hooks through an error,
只要你有深入的深度它就会被磨损
anytime that you have an exhaustive
depths thing, it's just worn.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 让我们来看看这对我们到底有什么用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's take a look
at what that actually does for us.
如果我说， >> Brian Holt: 如果 ，或者
If I say,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: if , or
就像这样我不知道然后我把它放进去
something like that, I don't know,
and then I put this in there,
它会说，嘿，看，或者这一个，在哪里 ?
it's gonna say, hey look, or
this one right here, where is it?
>> Brian Holt: 我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There we go.
有条件地调用 React 挂钩。
React hook is called conditionally.
必须以组件呈现的完全相同的顺序调用 React 挂钩。
React hooks must be called in the exact
same order in component renders.
你可以看到这来自于钩子的统治。
And you can see that
comes from rule of hooks.
>> Brian Holt: 挂钩规则，这有道理吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Rules of hooks,
that makes sense?
所以它会阻止你那样做
So it's gonna prevent you
from doing stuff like that.
>> Brian Holt: 老实说，一旦你习惯了这样做，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now honestly,
once you get used to doing that, and
你只知道永远不去做这也没那么有用
you just know never to do it,
it's not really that helpful.
但如你想象的那样如果你把这个船给你的同事
But as you may imagine, if you ship this
to your coworker that doesn't know about
这会阻止他们做你不想让他们做的事情
that, this will prevent them from doing
things that you don't want them to do.